learnwoo.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy - LearnWoo

Your privacy is important to us, and maintaining your trust and confidence is one of our highest priorities.

LearnWoo respects your right to keep your personal information confidential and we do not collect unnecessary personal information.

We do not share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop better features on our site, or to protect our rights.

We do not store personal information on our servers unless required for an operational feature of our site.

LearnWoo’s data privacy policy complies with the latest GDPR guidelines of the European Union.

#### Collection of non-personally identifying information

Like most websites, LearnWoo collects non-personally-identifying information such as demographics, device and browser type, language preference, referring sites, and the date and time of each visitor session. We collect this information to understand the interests of users and to see how different users make use of our website in a different manner.

#### Collection of personally-identifying information

LearnWoo collects name and email address of customers when they register on our site. We use this data to send you the information you requested.

When you enter a contest or other promotional features, we ask for your name, address and e-mail address to manage the contest and notify the winners.

We monitor traffic patterns and site usage to gain insights that would enable us to update the design and layout of the site.

LearnWoo will send you promotional email about new articles, special offers or other information periodically, which we think you may find interesting on the email address you have provided.

From time to time, we will also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. This information will help us customize the website according to your interests.

#### Disclosure of personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission, or are required by law to do so.

Occasionally, we use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting. However, we will take your prior consent in order to do so.

#### Cookies

“Cookies” are tiny bits of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on the LearnWoo site.

#### Changes in Privacy Policy

By using our website, you agree to the collection and use of this information by LearnWoo. In the event of we are deciding to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://learnwoo.com/contact-us/).
